Guide to the William S. Johnson Papers
Stanford University. Libraries.
- Papers
  - Schmid, Rudolf (Box 26, Folder 13)
  - Schmiegel, Klaus K. (Box 26, Folder 14)
  - Schmitz, Francis J. (Box 26, Folder 15)
  - Schneider, William P. (Box 26, Folder 16)
  - Schubert, Ulrich (Box 26, Folder 17)
  - Scott, John W. (Box 26, Folder 18)
  - Semmelhac, Martin F. (Box 26, Folder 19)
  - Sen, Stephanie (Box 26, Folder 20)
  - Shaffer, Paul R. (Box 26, Folder 21)
  - Shahak, Israel (Box 26, Folder 22)
  - Sharpe, Robert W. (Box 26, Folder 23)
  - Shelberg, Wesley E. (Box 26, Folder 24)
  - Shenvi, Ashok (Box 26, Folder 25)
  - Silverman, I. Robert (Box 26, Folder 26)
  - Small, Vernon (Box 26, Folder 27)
  - Snell, Brian W. (Box 26, Folder 28)
  - Staskun, Benjamin (Box 26, Folder 29)
  - Steele, John (Box 26, Folder 30)
  - Stelling, Gary D. (Box 26, Folder 31)
  - Stephens, Lawrence J. (Box 26, Folder 32)
  - Stern, Walter (Box 27, Folder 1)
  - Stipanovic, Robert D. (Box 27, Folder 2)
  - Stromberg, Verner L. (Box 27, Folder 3)
  - Sudhakar, Anatha (Box 27, Folder 4)
  - Sultanbawa, M. U. S. (Box 27, Folder 5)
  - Swoboda, Hans (Box 27, Folder 6)
  - Szmuszkovicz, Jacob (Box 27, Folder 7)
  - Tarney, Robert E. (Box 27, Folder 8)
  - Tebby, John C. (Box 27, Folder 9)
  - Telfer, Stephen (Box 27, Folder 10)
  - Thakur, Raghunath S. (Box 27, Folder 11)
  - Thompson, Michael D. (Box 27, Folder 12)
  - Truett, William (Box 27, Folder 13)
  - Trullinger, Dan (Box 27, Folder 14)
  - Tsatsos, William T. (Box 27, Folder 15)
  - Valasco, Mercedes (Box 27, Folder 16)
  - van der Gen, Arne (Box 27, Folder 17)
  - Volkmann, Robert (Box 27, Folder 18)
  - Vredenburgh, Walter A. (Box 27, Folder 19)
  - Wahl, Volker (Box 27, Folder 20)
  - Wang, Zhi-Qin (Box 27, Folder 21)
  - Ward, Carl E. (Box 27, Folder 22)
  - Warnhoff, Edgar W. (Box 27, Folder 23)
  - Wat, Edward K. W. (Box 27, Folder 24)
  - Welch, John (Box 27, Folder 25)
  - Werthemann, Lucius (Box 27, Folder 26)
  - Wetterau, William F. (Box 27, Folder 27)
  - Whitlock, Howard (Box 27, Folder 28)
  - Wiedhaup, Koenraad (Box 27, Folder 29)
  - Wightman, Robert H. (Box 27, Folder 30)
  - Williamson, Kenneth L. (Box 27, Folder 31)
  - Willy, W. Edward (Box 27, Folder 32)
  - Wittwer, Fritz (Box 27, Folder 33)
  - Wood, W. David (Box 28, Folder 1)
  - Woodhouse, Robert N. (Box 28, Folder 2)
  - Wolf, Hans (Box 28, Folder 3)
  - Wolfe, Andrew (Box 28, Folder 4)
  - Wulfman, David S. (Box 28, Folder 5)
  - Wynberg, Hans (Box 28, Folder 6)
  - Yarnell, Thomas M. (Box 28, Folder 7)
  - Yorka, Kenneth (Box 28, Folder 8)
  - Miscellaneous A-G (Box 28, Folder 9)
  - Miscellaneous H-M (Box 28, Folder 10)
  - Miscellaneous N-Z (Box 28, Folder 11)
  - Johnson Collaborators Reunion 1959 (Box 28, Folder 12)
  - Student research report: Marshall (Box 28, Folder 13)
  - Student research report: Ireland (Box 28, Folder 14)
  - Student research report: Cohen (Box 28, Folder 15)
  - Student research report: Bartlett (Box 28, Folder 16)
  - Student research report: Bull (Box 28, Folder 17)
  - Student research report: Dumas (Box 28, Folder 18)
  - Student research report: Dolak (Box 28, Folder 19)
  - Student research report: Faulkner (Box 28, Folder 20)
  - Student research report: Hudrlik (Box 28, Folder 21)
  - Student research report: Huntrakul (Box 28, Folder 22)
  - Student research report: Katner (Box 28, Folder 23)
  - Student research report: Kreutzer (Box 28, Folder 24)
  - Student research report: Jones (Box 28, Folder 25)
  - Student research report: Hooz (Box 28, Folder 26)
  - Student research report: Hamon (Box 28, Folder 27)
  - Student research report: Gelotte (Box 28, Folder 28)
  - Student research report: Fitzi (Box 28, Folder 29)
  - Student research report: Eade (Box 28, Folder 30)
  - Student research report: Burckhardt (Box 28, Folder 31)
  - Student research report: Coverdale (Box 28, Folder 32)
  - Student research report: De Jongh (Box 28, Folder 33)
  - Student research report: Campbell (Box 28, Folder 34)
  - Student research report: Cox (Box 28, Folder 35)
  - Student research report: Crosby (Box 28, Folder 36)
  - Student research report: Snell (Box 28, Folder 37)
  - Student research report: Sultanbawa (Box 28, Folder 38)
  - Student research report: Sultanbawa (Box 28, Folder 39)
  - Student research report: Shahak (Box 28, Folder 40)
  - Student research report: Schubert (Box 29, Folder 1)
  - Student research report: Schiess (Box 29, Folder 2)
  - Student research report: Schmitz (Box 29, Folder 3)
  - Student research report: Scott (Box 29, Folder 4)
  - Student research report: Werthemann (Box 29, Folder 5)
  - Student research report: Williamson (Box 29, Folder 6)
  - Student research report: Wahl (Box 29, Folder 7)
  - Student research report: Olson (Box 29, Folder 8)
  - Student research report: Owyan (Box 29, Folder 9)
  - Student research report: Rizzi (Box 29, Folder 10)
  - Student research report: Stern (Box 29, Folder 11)
  - Student research report: Lazar (Box 29, Folder 12)
  - Student research report: Markezich (Box 29, Folder 13)
  - Student research report: Metcalf (Box 29, Folder 14)
  - Student research report: Della (Box 29, Folder 15)
  - Student research report: Dunathan (Box 29, Folder 16)
  - Student research report: Molloy (Box 29, Folder 17)
  - Student research report: Miles & Bryson (Box 29, Folder 18)
  - Student research report: Edington (Box 29, Folder 19)
  - Johnson reprints (Box 29, Folder 20)